Hello hello brother, yes this is the Facebook page of sesame,
I am using it since 3 years, 3
years ago I have a lot of pimples, so
my dermatologist suggested this to me,
so I have ordered this from Amazon
now and let me tell you that
my skin is very oily, so this is
for oily hair, people with
dry skin should not use it or you can see it is
written on it, skin whitening also
planing, special power, paraben free, air
flight is also free, this cost me around
200 rupees and the bigger one of 200ml costs
500 something, but this
face wash works very well on my skin
and it seriously body planing
your skin, so its oily skin
and those who have pimples along with flesh can
use it.